

#### Md Sajedul Haque Romy

Hesse Str 12, 90443, Nuremberg +491776066565 romi0199@gmail.com https://sajedul-romy.netlify.app/ github.com/codebangla

## Summary

Seasoned, forward-looking Software Engineer with a background of 3+ years in creating and implementing innovative software solutions to enhance business success. Committed to maintaining effective communication and intend to learn from the team. Actively looking for a full-time position and also having an EU-Blue card.

## Experience

<u>Incadea Gmbh</u> (Junior Frontend Developer) Munich, Germany (Remote)

Oct 2022 -Present

- Write new Frontend features for a POC with Angular 13 using Carbon framework, RxJS, HTML, CSS3, JavaScript for .NET WEB API REStful API Backend in a scrum environment, informing the software architect to enable CORS policy of Backend. This POC is about a Customer feedback system including dashboard.
- Write necessary unit test using Karma to check the functionalities of the features, components and services
- Write necessary documentation for other developers for collaboration in Azure DevOPS environment

Up2u Gmbh (Werkstudent Full-stack Developer) Nuremberg, Germany

Jun 2021 - Jun 2022

- Integrated Google map JavaScript API for future POC for a B2B and B2C platform
- Created Backend with C#, ASP.NET Web API, Entity Framework code first migration, .NET Core 6.0
- Developed Web components with Angular 13 and Bootstrap, Typescript, HTML and CSS3

Togumogu LTD (Software Developer) Dhaka, Bangladesh

Aug 2018- Mar 2020

- Developed ecommerce application Angular 8 from RESTful Web APIs and implemented new features using based on requirements
- Conceptualized and wrote technical documentation as well as dynamic usability solutions as part of an agile Scrum team
- Wrote Unit Tests with Jasmine and Karma for quality assurance for CD/CI

# **Projects**

NgNet -NgNET is a boilerplate application featuring Docker, Angular 15 frontend with hot reload, Bootstrap 5, .NET 7.0 Web REStful Api backend, automatic PostgreSQL database migration, and PgAdmin StrapStone - Full-stack job portal POC application with Angular 13, Bootstrap 5.0, C#, ASP.NET Core 5.0. Frontend has Angular Reactive form and protected routes, http interceptions, shared components. The app has JWT Authentication and backend Authorization, CRUD operation, Toast notification features.

### Education

MSc in Medical Engineering (Medical Imaging and Data Processing) (part-time)

Apr 2020 - Mar 2022

Friedrich-Alexander-Universität Erlangen-Nürnberg, Germany

**BSc in Computer Science and Engineering** 

University of Information Technology and Sciences, Bangladesh

Apr 2012 - May 2017

## **Technical Skills and Tools**

**Development:** JavaScript, TypeScript, NodeJS, Angular, Ionic Angular, RxJS, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Bootstrap, Material UI, C#, .NET Core, ASP.NET MVC, WEB API, REST API, SQL Server, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Git, xUnit, Jasmine, Karma, Cypress, Webpack

Deployment: Azure Cloud, Docker, Circle CI, IIS, TFS

Tools: Visual Studio, VS Code, Git, Postman, Photoshop, Miro, SSMS, Pg Admin, Jira, Confluence